gomohu.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy

**Mohu’s Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to Mohu. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that describes what information we collect on Mohu websites, via Mohu products and/or Mohu applications and how we use that information.

Please note that Mohu’s Privacy Policy does not cover any third parties, their products, actions, or their services and cannot control how third parties collect, use or secure your data.

**I.  Information Collection**

**Information you provide**

Information we may collect from you through the Mohu website, Mohu products, and Mohu Applications include items such as your name, email address, billing and shipping information, product purchase information, credit card and other payment data, and product registration information.

**Information we collect automatically**

We may also automatically collect information related to the use of Mohu websites such as your computer’s operating system, IP address, access times, browser type and language, and the websites you visited before coming to the Mohu website. We also use cookies to better understand your needs.  A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on your computer hard drive that includes a unique identifier. Cookies enable Mohu and others to track usage patterns and deliver customized content, marketing, and advertising to you.  We also collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on Mohu Sites or in our emails.  We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, to understand usage of Mohu Sites, products and services and the effectiveness of Mohu Site features and campaigns, and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

We regularly and automatically upload information from your Mohu Device and your usage. The collected information includes the IP address associated with your Mohu Device, your device type and model, specific identifiers that tell us what content you play, including time and duration played, various quality measures, error logs, software version numbers, and other usage statistics. Usage information uploaded from Mohu Devices is personally identifiable by product serial number. In some instances, serial numbers are associated with personally identifiable information, and we can often tell from the serial number at what store and location you purchased your Mohu Device.  
If you download Mohu Mobile Applications, we also automatically log information related to your mobile device and network. We may log, for example, your device type, device identifiers, Wi-Fi networking connection data, information about connected Wi-Fi devices, the types and versions of mobile operating system you use, time-stamped logs of data exchanges, and usage statistics.

**Online Advertising**

We may use information collected using third party cookies and Web beacons on Mohu Sites and in our emails to deliver Mohu advertising displayed to you on third party sites. We also use cookie information to know when you return to Mohu Sites after visiting these third party sites. We use this information and other information about you to try to understand your interests and show you relevant advertising and information about products and services offered by Mohu and its partners.

Certain third party ad networks may automatically collect information about your visits to Mohu Sites and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, and the browser you use to visit Mohu Sites (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number). They do this using cookies, Web beacons or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising relevant to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of Mohu Sites and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or Web beacons in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click here:  <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

**II.  Information Usage**

Information collected by Mohu is used by Mohu and others on Mohu’s behalf for the following purposes:

  * to understand how you are using our products and services in order to make them better,
  * to personalize your experience, to offer you relevant content, recommendations, and display marketing and advertising tailored to your preferences,
  * to fulfill your orders and to provide customer support,
  * for marketing purposes such as to send you emails about products, events, promotions and offers from Mohu and its partners,
  * to send you service information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages,
  * to respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service,
  * for analyzing marketing effectiveness, product usage, feature popularity, software quality, and to improve and influence the design of future products, and
  * to protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.

**III.  Information Access and Choices**

If you wish to ask for access, correction, or deletion of any of your personal information held by us or a change in the way we use your information, please contact us at:  support@gomohu.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to respond to your request in a timely manner. However, even if Mohu deletes such personal information from its ‘live’ database, it may still be stored on other redundant databases (including those kept for archival purposes).

When you visit Mohu Sites, we and others give you the following choices about use of mechanisms for tracking, including tracking of your online activities over time and across different websites and online services by third parties. Many Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies from Mohu servers. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of Mohu Sites. To learn about opting-out of certain third party analytics tracking on the Mohu Sites, see, for example:  <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>, <https://www.optimizely.com/opt_out>, and <http://www.bazaarvoice.com/privacy-policy/#whatarecookies>, and <https://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out>.  You can also choose to opt-out of use of cookies by many of Mohu’s third party advertising partners to deliver ads tailored to your profile and preferences by clicking here:  <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. If you delete your cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choices.  If you do not want us to track emails we send you, some email services let you change your display to turn off HTML or disable download of images which should effectively disable our email tracking, or you may unsubscribe from our marketing emails as described in those emails. While we and others give you choices described in this Privacy Policy, there are many ways Web browser signals and other similar mechanisms can indicate your choice to disable tracking, and we may not be aware of or honor every mechanism.

**IV.  Data Storage and Security**

Mohu uses industry-standard methods of securing its electronic databases of personal information. However, you should know that no company, including Mohu, can fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information.  To help protect yourself, please use a strong password, do not use the same passwords to access your Mohu accounts that you use with other accounts or services, and protect your user names and passwords to help prevent others from accessing your accounts and services.

**V.   Your California Privacy Rights**

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (a “California Customer”) may request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.  In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.  California Customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [support@gomohu.com](mailto:support@gomohu.com).  Please note that we are required to respond to one request per California Customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

**VI.  Modifications**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended version on our websites.
